(Q31（单选）) ⭐ as it's more commonly known = 正如大家更熟悉的称呼（C1）｜monosodium glutamate (MSG) = 谷氨酸钠
⭐ flavour enhancer = 增味剂（C1）｜be used particularly in... = 尤其用于……（B2）
[Q31答案句， the way ... = how ... works] ⭐ explore = 探究；深入研究（C1）｜cuisine = 菜系；饮食文化（C1）｜enhance = 提升；增强（C1）
(Q32) ⭐ the main reason why... = ……的主要原因
⭐ incorporate sth in/into sth = 将某物加入；融入某物（C1）｜a type of...known as... = 一种被称为……的……｜have the ability to do sth = 具有做某事的能力（B2）
[Q32答案句] ⭐ It wasn't until...that... = 直到……才……（C1，非常重要句型）｜be responsible for = 对……负责；导致……（B2）｜improvement in flavour = 味道提升
(Q33) ⭐ commercially = 商业化地（C1）｜means of extraction = 提取方式（C1）
[Q33答案句] ⭐ It was in...that... = 正是在……（强调句型）｜increase dramatically = 大幅增长（C1）｜to this day = 直到今天（C1）
⭐ hundreds of thousands of = 数十万的（B2）｜all over the world = 世界各地
(Q34（notes）) ⭐ what exactly is...? = ……究竟是什么？
[Q34答案句] ⭐ contain = 包含（B2）｜per cent = 百分比
(Q35&36) [Q35答案句] ⭐ be found naturally in = 天然存在于（B2）｜protein-containing foods = 含蛋白质的食物（C1）
(Q37) ⭐ It is widely known that... = 众所周知……（C1）｜be aware that... = 意识到……（B2）｜other parts of the world = 世界其他地区
⭐ commercially made = 商业制作的（C1）｜things like... = 类似……的东西（B2）
⭐ how exactly does...work? = ……究竟如何运作？
⭐ be familiar with = 熟悉（B2）｜concept = 概念（B2）
[Q37答案句] ⭐ identify = 发现；确认（C1）
(Q38) ⭐ It is thought that... = 人们认为……（C1）｜intensify = 加强；增强（C1）｜naturally occurring = 自然存在的（C1）
[Q38答案句] ⭐ make perfect sense = 完全合理（C1）｜evolutionary sense = 进化意义（C1）｜have the ability to detect = 具有检测……的能力（C1）｜most common = 最常见的
(Q39) ⭐ associate professor = 副教授｜serve a purpose = 发挥作用；有用途（C1）
⭐ signal the presence of... = 表明……的存在（C1）｜in the same way that... = 以同样方式……（B2）｜energy-giving = 提供能量的（C1）
[Q39答案句] ⭐ alert sb of/about sth = 提醒某人注意某事（C1）｜toxin = 毒素（C1）
(Q40) [Q40答案句] ⭐ warn sb of sth = 警告某人某事（B2）｜spoilage = 腐坏；变质（C1）｜signal the presence of... = 表明……存在（C1）
⭐ what else do we know about...? = 关于……还有什么了解？（B2）